[
{
   "category": "arrayMethods",
   "questionText": "What does the array method .every() do?",
   "answerText": "accepts a function as an argument. Returns a boolean. Returns true if all pass"
},
{
    "category": "arrayMethods",
    "questionText": "What does the array method .concat() do?",
    "answerText": "accepts two arrays as arguments. It combines them and returns the combined array"
},
{
   "category": "arrayMethods",
   "questionText": "What does the array method .filter() do?",
   "answerText": "Accepts a function as an argument. Returns a boolean. If all elements pass returns true"
},
{
   "category": "arrayMethods",
   "questionText": "What does the array method .find() do?",
   "answerText": "Accepts a function as an argument and returns the first element that passes"
},
{
   "category": "arrayMethods",
   "questionText": "What does the array method .findIndex do?",
   "answerText": "accepts a function as an argument and returns the index of the first element that passes"
},
{
   "category": "arrayMethods",
   "questionText": "What does the array method .flat() do?",
   "answerText": "If one or more elements of an array are themselves arrays, get's rid of these subarrays and turns the elements in the subarrays into elements in the main array"
},
{
   "category": "arrayMethods",
   "questionText": "What does the array method .forEach() do?",
   "answerText": "Accepts a function as an argument and calls that function on each element of the array"
},
{
   "category": "stringMethods",
   "questionText": "What does the string method .join() do?",
   "answerText": "accepts a string as an argument and combines it with the string it was called on"
},
{
   "category": "stringMethods",
   "questionText": "What does the string method .charAt() do?",
   "answerText": "returns the chrachter at a specified index"
},
{
   "category": "stringMethods",
   "questionText": "What does the string method .slice() do?",
   "answerText": "accepts two indexes as arguments. returns the characters in between. character at first index is not included. Charachter at last index is"
},
{
   "category": "es6",
   "questionText": "What is a arrow or fat arrow function?",
   "answerText": "a function in the format: (arguments) => {function body}"
},
{
   "category": "es6",
   "questionText": "What is the functionality are let and const?",
   "answerText": "block scoped. const is immutable."
},
{
   "category": "es6",
   "questionText": "what are template string?",
   "answerText": "strings in the format: `some text ${variable}`"
},
{
   "category": "es6",
   "questionText": "what is a for of loop?",
   "answerText": "loops through iterable values like strings and arrays"
},
{
   "category": "react",
   "questionText": "what is the syntax of react?",
   "answerText": "JSX"
},
{
   "category": "react",
   "questionText": "what two things can define a javascript component",
   "answerText": "function and Class"
},
{
   "category": "react",
   "questionText": "What should be added to list items so that javascript can tell if the list has changed",
   "answerText": "Keys"
}
]